Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not Annotated
      - R
        - Red Dragon - A can't get boe, 1991; SR-23864; Red Dragon (Box 410)
          Catalog # VPRD-860; A-side Matrix # VPRD 860-A CANT GET BOE
          Dragon Records
        - Red Dragon - Agony, 1987; SR-23865; Red Dragon; Techniques All Stars (Box 410)
          In same jacket as # SR-23866. Different discs.
          Catalog # WR-agony-A; A-side Matrix # WR-agony-A Kkmastering
        - Sanchez - Dungle lover, 1987; SR-23866; Sanchez; Flourgon (Box 410)
          In same jacket as # SR-23865. Different discs.
          Catalog # none; A-side Matrix # WR-DM96 Lover-A-Kkmastering
        - Red Dragon - Duck dance, 1988; SR-23867; Red Dragon (Box 410)
          Catalog # LLDIS 78; A-side Matrix # LLD 78 A
          Live And Love
          London, England
        - Red Dragon - Agony, 1987; SR-29724; Red Dragon; Techniques All Stars (Box 410)
          In same jacket as # SR-29725. Different discs.
          Catalog # WR-agony-A; A-side Matrix # WR-agony-A- Kkmastering
        - Red Dragon - Agony, 1987; SR-29725; Red Dragon; Techniques All Stars (Box 410)
          In same jacket as # SR-29724. Different discs.
          Catalog # 92-26832; A-side Matrix # WRT24A PA2608-MT WRT-24A-1
        - Red Eye - Rebel call, 1994; SR-23868; Red Eye (Box 410)
          Catalog # RTR01LP; A-side Matrix # RTR-01-A
          Round Table Records
        - Red Fox - As a matter of Fox (Disc one), 1993; SR-23869; Red Fox (Box 410)
          In same jacket as # SR-23870. Double album.
          Catalog # 61531-1; A-side Matrix # ST-E-61531-A1
        - Red Fox - As a matter of Fox (Disc two), 1993; SR-23870; Red Fox (Box 410)
          In same jacket as # SR-23869. Double album.
          Catalog # 61531-1; A-side Matrix # ST-E-61531-C1
        - Red Fox - As a matter of Fox (Disc one), 1993; SR-23871; Red Fox (Box 410)
          In same jacket as # SR-23872. Double album.
        - Red Fox - As a matter of Fox (Disc two), 1993; SR-23872; Red Fox (Box 410)
          In same jacket as # SR-23871. Double album.
        - Red Fox - Let's chill; Blood for money, 1991; SR-23873; Red Fox; Naturally (Box 410)
          Catalog # SIG125; A-side Matrix # SIG-125-A LETS CHIL VP-CM
          Signet Records
        - Red Handed - Horny (on me), 2004; SR-23874; Red Handed; DJ Red Handed (Box 410)
          Catalog # Capri 001-1; A-side Matrix # CAPRI-001-01-A
          No Kid'n Records
        - Red Hot Chili Peppers - Fight like a brave, 1987; SR-23875; Red Hot Chili Peppers (Box 410)
          Catalog # 12EA 214; A-side Matrix # 12EA 214 A-1-1-3
          EMI-Manhattan Records
        - Red Hot Chili Peppers - Fight like a brave (not our mix), 1987; SR-23876; Red Hot Chili Peppers (Box 410)
          Catalog # V-56076; A-side Matrix # V-1-56076-P2 B-29316-P2 18444 0-1
        - Red Hot Chili Peppers - Freaky styley, 2000; SR-23877; Red Hot Chili Peppers (Box 410)
          Catalog # SVLP 223; A-side Matrix # 08 44084 20 1A1 SVLP 223
          Simply Vinyl
        - Red Hot Lover Tone - Wanna make moves, 1995; SR-23878; Red Hot Lover Tone (Box 410)
          Catalog # 25043-1; A-side Matrix #
        - Red Hot Lover Lover Tone - Red Hot Lover Lover Tone, 1992; SR-23879; Red Hot Lover Lover Tone (Box 410)
          Catalog # 1-21644; A-side Matrix # 1-21644 A
        - Red Light District - I know, 1996; SR-23880; Red Light District (Box 410)
          Catalog # none; A-side Matrix # RED-001-A
          Get Live Entertainment
        - Red Lorry Yellow Lorry - Walking on your hands, 1986; SR-23881; Red Lorry Yellow Lorry (Box 410)
          Catalog # REDT 66; A-side Matrix # MPO REDT 66 A^ ….AND STILL BEATING OUR HEADS!
          Red Rhino Records
          York, England
        - Red Plastic Bag - Master stroke, 2001; SR-23882; Red Plastic Bag (Box 410)
          Catalog # BF 055; A-side Matrix # FUTENKAMMAN A RPB EAB 374
          Bayfield
        - Red Rat - I'm a big kid now, 2000; SR-23883; Red Rat (Box 410)
          Catalog # GREL 260; A-side Matrix # GREL260A-1
        - Red Rat - Island boy, 2000; SR-23884; Red Rat; Treach (Box 410)
          Catalog # RR001P; A-side Matrix # RR001P A
        - Red Rockets - Till it all falls down, 1983; SR-23885; Red Rockets (Box 410)
          Catalog # AS 1732; A-side Matrix # XXS 169432-1A
        - Red Snapper - Bogeyman, 1998; SR-23886; Red Snapper (Box 410)
          Catalog # WAP104; A-side Matrix # WAP 104 A-1-1-
          Warp Records
        - Red Snapper - Loopascoopa (Disc one), 1996; SR-23887; Red Snapper (Box 410)
          In same jacket as # SR-23888. Double album.
          Catalog # Wap 84; A-side Matrix # MPO WAP 84 A1
        - Red Snapper - Loopascoopa (Disc two), 1996; SR-23888; Red Snapper (Box 410)
          In same jacket as # SR-23887. Double album.
          Catalog # Wap 84; A-side Matrix # MPO WAP 84 C1
        - Red Snapper - Making bones (Disc two), 1998; SR-23889; Red Snapper (Box 410)
          Catalog # WARP LP 56; A-side Matrix # WARPLP 56C-01-1-
        - Redbone - Come and get your Redbone the best of Redbone (Disc one), 1975; SR-23890; Redbone (Box 410)
          In same jacket as # SR-23891. Double album.
          Catalog # KEG 33456; A-side Matrix # P AL-33457-1C
        - Redbone - Come and get your Redbone the best of Redbone (Disc two), 1975; SR-23891; Redbone (Box 410)
          In same jacket as # SR-23890. Double album.
          Catalog # KEG 33456; A-side Matrix # P AL-33458-1C
        - Redd, Jeff - I found lovin', 1989; SR-23892; Redd, Jeff (Box 410)
          Catalog # MCA-23985; A-side Matrix # MCA-9626-A-SS1
        - Redd, Sharon - Beat the street, 1982; SR-23893; Redd, Sharon (Box 410)
          Catalog # PRL D 563; A-side Matrix # PRLD-563-AS
          Prelude Records
        - Redd, Sharon - Can't dance (dance, dance, dance), 1977; SR-23894; Redd, Sharon; Hedwig, Ula (Box 410)
          Catalog # AS 413; A-side Matrix # XSS 162161-1D
        - Redd, Sharon - In the name of love, 1982; SR-23895; Redd, Sharon (Box 410)
          Catalog # PRLD 569; A-side Matrix # PRLD-569-1
        - Redd, Sharon - Formerly of the Harlettes, 1978; SR-23896; Redd, Sharon; Hedwig, Ula (Box 410)
          Catalog # JC 35250; A-side Matrix # PAL 35250-1B S1 SX
        - Reddings - Call the law, 1988; SR-23897; Reddings (Box 410)
          In same jacket as # SR-23898. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 887 681-1; A-side Matrix # 887 681-1AS SP
        - Reddings - Call the law, 1988; SR-23898; Reddings (Box 410)
          In same jacket as # SR-23897. 2 copies.
        - Reddings - So in love with you, 1988; SR-23899; Reddings (Box 410)
          Catalog # 887 395-1; A-side Matrix # 887 395 1 AS SP
        - Reddings - Moon rock, 1983; SR-23900; Reddings (Box 410)
          Catalog # AS 1788; A-side Matrix # P XSM 171488 1A
          Believe In A Dream
        - Reddings - I know you got another, 1982; SR-23901; Reddings (Box 410)
          Catalog # AS 1406; A-side Matrix # XSM-170015-1B
        - Redd's And The Boys - Hitt'n and holding live, 1985; SR-23902; Redd's And The Boys (Box 410)
          In same jacket as # SR-23903. 2 copies.
          Catalog # LZ-999; A-side Matrix # LZ-999-A
          Love Boat Records
        - Redd's And The Boys - Hitt'n and holding live, 1985; SR-23903; Redd's And The Boys (Box 410)
          In same jacket as # SR-23902. 2 copies.
        - Redds & The Boys - Movin' & groovin', 1985; SR-23904; Redds & The Boys (Box 411)
          Catalog # PRO-205; A-side Matrix # A-1 PRO-205-A HRM
          4th & Broadway
        - Redds & The Boys - Movin' & groovin', 1985; SR-23905; Redds & The Boys (Box 411)
        - Reddy, Helen - Make love to me, 1979; SR-23906; Reddy, Helen (Box 411)
          Catalog # SPRO-9117; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9117 F1
        - Redhead Kingpin And The FBI - Get it together, 1991; SR-23907; Redhead Kingpin And The FBI (Box 411)
          Catalog # DMD 1604; A-side Matrix # STDM 60080-81-82-1
          Virgin Records America, Inc.
        - Redhead Kingpin And The FBI - Nice & slow, 1991; SR-23908; Redhead Kingpin And The FBI (Box 411)
          Catalog # DMD 1733; A-side Matrix # STDM 61117 61115-1
        - Redhead Kingpin And The FBI - We don't have a plan B; All about Red, 1990; SR-23909; Redhead Kingpin And The FBI (Box 411)
          Catalog # DMD 1599; A-side Matrix # STDM-59787-59788-1 DSM
          Virgin
        - Redhead Kingpin And The FBI - Nice & slow, 1991; SR-23910; Redhead Kingpin And The FBI (Box 411)
        - Redman - Tonight's da night, 1992; SR-23911; Redman (Box 411)
          Catalog # OAS 5141; A-side Matrix # XSS-05141-A-1A
          Def Jam Recordings
        - Redman - Let's get dirty (I can't get in da club), 2000; SR-23912; Redman; DJ Kool (Box 411)
          Catalog # 314572917-1; A-side Matrix # 314-572-917-1-A1 DEFR-15297-1 A
        - Redman - The saga continues, 2003; SR-23913; Redman (Box 411)
          Catalog # REDMAN-0011; A-side Matrix # REDMAN 0011-1-A
        - Redman - Doc's da name 2000 (Disc one), 1998; SR-23914; Redman (Box 411)
          In same jacket as # SR-23915. Double album.
          Catalog # 314 558 945-1; A-side Matrix # 314-558-946-1-A
          Def Jam Music Group
        - Redman - Doc's da name 2000 (Disc two), 1998; SR-23915; Redman (Box 411)
          In same jacket as # SR-23914. Double album.
          Catalog # 314 558 945-1; A-side Matrix # 314-558-947-1-A
        - Redman - Blow your mind, 1992; SR-23916; Redman (Box 411)
          In same jacket as # SR-23917. 2 copies.
          Catalog # AOD 74424; A-side Matrix # XSS-74424-A-1A
          Rush Associated Labels
        - Redman - Blow your mind, 1992; SR-23917; Redman (Box 411)
          In same jacket as # SR-23916. 2 copies.
        - Redman - F*k da security, 2005; SR-23918; Redman (Box 411)
          Catalog # DEFR 16422-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16422-1-REI
        - Redman - Whateva man, 1996; SR-23919; Redman (Box 411)
          Catalog # 314 574 027-1; A-side Matrix # 314-574-027-1-A
        - Redman - Tear it off, 1999; SR-23920; Redman (Box 411)
          Catalog # CAS 42632; A-side Matrix # XSS-42632-A
        - Redman - Malpractice (Disc one), 2001; SR-23921; Redman (Box 411)
          In same jacket as # SR-23922. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFF 15265-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-15266-1-A
        - Redman - Malpractice (Disc two), 2001; SR-23922; Redman (Box 411)
          In same jacket as # SR-23921. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFF 15265-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-15267-1-A
        - Reed, J. Michael - Reach out for love; Dancin' in the sky (in New York City), 1979; SR-23923; Reed, J. Michael (Box 411)
          Catalog # NBD 20197 DJ; A-side Matrix # NBD-20197-AS
        - Reed, Jerry - Ko-Ko Joe, 1971; SR-23924; Reed, Jerry (Box 411)
          Catalog # LSP-4596; A-side Matrix # APRS-1704-4S-A3 D
          RCA Victor
        - Reed, Jerry - When you're hot, you're hot, 1971; SR-23925; Reed, Jerry (Box 411)
          Catalog # LPS-4506; A-side Matrix # APRS-1169-1S-A1A
        - Reed, Lou - Metal Machine Music (The Amine β Ring) (Disc one), 1975; SR-23926; Reed, Lou (Box 411)
          In same jacket as # SR-23927. Double album.
          Catalog # CPL2-1101; A-side Matrix # CPL 2 1101 A 4
        - Reed, Lou - Metal Machine Music (The Amine β Ring) (Disc two), 1975; SR-23927; Reed, Lou (Box 411)
          In same jacket as # SR-23926. Double album.
          Catalog # CPL2-1101; A-side Matrix # CPL 2 1101 B 4
        - Reed, Lou - The blue mask, 1982; SR-23928; Reed, Lou (Box 411)
          Catalog # AFL1 4221; A-side Matrix # AFL1 4221-A
        - Reed, Vivian - Start dancin', 1978; SR-23929; Reed, Vivian (Box 411)
          Catalog # SP-189; A-side Matrix # SP-189-1- RE
          United Artists Records
        - Reef Hustle - Thro it back (my house); Un' stan' me, 2002; SR-23930; Reef Hustle (Box 411)
          Catalog # none; A-side Matrix # MR-001-A EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 61707 DON GROSSINGER
          Monsta Records
        - K-Reen - Choisis; A l'interieur, 1997; SR-23931; K-Reen (Box 411)
          In same jacket as # SR-23932. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DM001; A-side Matrix # D FI-97-6 D M 001 A
          Defrey Productions
        - K-Reen - Choisis; A l'interieur, 1997; SR-23932; K-Reen (Box 411)
          In same jacket as # SR-23931. 2 copies.
        - Reeno - S.M.D., 2003; SR-23933; Reeno; Mr. X (Box 411)
          Catalog # SP 001; A-side Matrix # SP-001-A-RE EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 74270 DON GROSSINGER
          Spazzoid Records
        - Reese - Just want another chance, 1988; SR-23934; Reese (Box 411)
          Catalog # IR 111787; A-side Matrix # IR-111787-A
          Incognito Records
        - Reeves, Dianne - Never too far, 1987; SR-23935; Reeves, Dianne (Box 411)
          Catalog # E1-92401; A-side Matrix # E1-1-92401-21
          EMI USA
        - Reflections - Boogie city; I'm gonna let yo go this time, 1978; SR-23936; Reflections (Box 411)
          Catalog # JD-11409; A-side Matrix # PD-11409A-1
        - Reflex One - Breakbeat sessions vol three, 2001; SR-23937; Reflex One (Box 411)
          Catalog # VIC 14; A-side Matrix # VIC-14-A1
          Strickly Dubz
        - Melky and Day - I got a love jones (remixes), 1997; SR-23938; Melky and Day; Refugee Camp All Stars (Box 411)
          Catalog # CAS 0479; A-side Matrix # XSS-0479A-1B RJ
        - Refugee Camp All Stars - The sweetest thing (mahogany mix), 1997; SR-23939; Refugee Camp All Stars; Hill, Lauryn (Box 411)
          Catalog # CAS 0877; A-side Matrix # XSS-0877-A
        - Melky and Day - I got a love jones (remixes), 1997; SR-23940; Melky and Day; Refugee Camp All Stars (Box 411)
          Catalog # CAS 0479; A-side Matrix # XSS-0479A-1A RJ
        - Melky and Day - Love Jones, 1997; SR-23941; Melky and Day; Refugee Camp All Stars (Box 411)
          Catalog # CAS 9907; A-side Matrix # XSS-9907A-1A
        - Reggaenommix - New York Sept 84, 1984; SR-23942; Reggaenommix (Box 411)
          Catalog # CLAY LP 13; A-side Matrix # 84 8 CLAL LP 13 A1
          Clay Records
          Stroke-on-Trent, England
        - Reggy O. - Let the music play, 1993; SR-23943; Reggy O. (Box 411)
          Catalog # ZYX 7156-12; A-side Matrix # ZYX 7156-12 A
          ZYX Music
          Merenberg, Germany
        - Reggie Griffin & Technofunk - Mirda rock, 1982; SR-23944; Reggie Griffin & Technofunk (Box 411)
          Catalog # SM-604; A-side Matrix # VID-714-A
          Sweet Mountain Records
          Englewood, New Jersey
        - Reggie Griffin & Technofunk - Mirda rock, 1982; SR-23945; Reggie Griffin & Technofunk (Box 411)
          In same jacket as # SR-23946. 2 copies.
        - Reggie Griffin & Technofunk - Mirda rock, 1982; SR-23946; Reggie Griffin & Technofunk (Box 411)
          In same jacket as # SR-23945. 2 copies.
        - Regina - Baby love, 1986; SR-23947; Regina (Box 411)
          Catalog # DMD 939; A-side Matrix # ST-DM 49492-1 1-1
        - Regina - Head on, 1986; SR-23948; Regina (Box 411)
          Catalog # DMD 1011; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-51127-1 1-1
        - Regine - Je survivrai (I will survive), 1979; SR-23949; Regine (Box 411)
          Catalog # PDS 3; A-side Matrix # PDS-3A -STAMPER- FWCS K-10534 GOL
          Prism
        - Regine - Je survivrai (I will survive); I'll never stop dancin', 1979; SR-23950; Regine (Box 411)
        - Rehmi, TJ - The fuisonist, 1996; SR-23951; Rehmi, TJ (Box 411)
          Catalog # NR 84 T; A-side Matrix # NR 84T A1 The Exchange -Nilz
          Nation Records
        - Reid, Bert - Music on my mind, 1999; SR-23952; Reid, Bert (Box 411)
          Catalog # SOW-439; A-side Matrix # SOW 439 A
          Soundmen On Wax
        - Reid, Jr. - Cry now; Looking my love, 1994; SR-23953; Reid, Jr.; Barrington, Levy (Box 411)
          Catalog # RAS 7045; A-side Matrix # RAS-7045-A-RE-1
          RAS Records Inc.
        - Reid, Junior - Bubblers, 1995; SR-23954; Reid, Junior (Box 411)
          Catalog # MB-41; A-side Matrix # MB 041-A Bubblers Paul-VP
          Massive B
        - Reid, Junior - Bubblers, 1995; SR-23955; Reid, Junior (Box 411)
        - Reid, Junior - Bubblers, 1995; SR-23956; Reid, Junior (Box 411)
        - Reign - Indestructible, 1996; SR-23957; Reign (Box 411)
          Catalog # 119-341-004-1; A-side Matrix # 6-119-341-004-1-6A
          H.O.L.A. Recordings
        - Reign - Indestructible, 1996; SR-23958; Reign (Box 412)
          Catalog # 6-119-341-003-1-7; A-side Matrix # 6-119-341003 1-7-A
        - Reign - Touch and play, 1997; SR-23959; Reign (Box 412)
          Catalog # HPRO-41020; A-side Matrix # HPRO-41020A
        - Reilly, Trevor - Down with the underground, 1998; SR-23960; Reilly, Trevor (Box 412)
          Catalog # TRVDJ1; A-side Matrix # TRVDJ 1 A ORLAKE
          Manifesto
        - Relation Inc. - First love, only love, 1988; SR-23961; Relation Inc. (Box 412)
          Catalog # SE0101; A-side Matrix # QCA 8X328 ADF
          R&A Records
          Birmingham, Michigan
        - Relation Inc. - I think we're alone now, 1987; SR-23962; Relation Inc. (Box 412)
          Catalog # SE0100; A-side Matrix # QCA 701033XA - DOWNIE
        - R.E.M. - Losing my religion, 1991; SR-23963; R.E.M. (Box 412)
          Catalog # W 0015; A-side Matrix # W0015(T)-A-1
        - Remedy - Seen it all; Everything is real, 1997; SR-23964; Remedy (Box 412)
          Catalog # FAR 0666; A-side Matrix # FAR-0666-A
          Fifth Angel Recordings
        - Remixers - I.C. love affair, 1997; SR-23965; Remixers (Box 412)
          Catalog # DFC 1302; A-side Matrix # DFC 1302-A 131S
          DFC
          Bologna, Italy
        - Remy Ma - Conceited (there's something about Remy), 2005; SR-23966; Remy Ma (Box 412)
          Catalog # UNIR21524-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-21524-1A
        - Remy Ma - Conceited (there's something about Remy), 2005; SR-23967; Remy Ma (Box 412)
        - Ren - Calling my name (remix), 2002; SR-23968; Ren (Box 412)
          Catalog # 80246 90508 1 3; A-side Matrix # 80246-90508-1-3-A
          Music Mind Records
        - René & Angela - Wall to wall, 1981; SR-23969; René & Angela (Box 412)
          Catalog # SPRO-9682; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9682-97370 21 #1
        - René & Angela - Save your love (for #1), 1985; SR-23970; René & Angela (Box 412)
          Catalog # 880 731-1 DJ; A-side Matrix # 880 731-1-258167-ALD OB-21042-ALD SLM 9367 1-1
          Mercury
        - René & Angela - Your smile, 1985; SR-23971; René & Angela (Box 412)
          Catalog # 884 271-1; A-side Matrix # 884-271-1-2-58195 PRC-R -A-1-1-1-P1
        - René & Angela - I'll be good, 1985; SR-23972; René & Angela (Box 412)
          Catalog # 884 009-1 DJ; A-side Matrix # 884 009-1 DJ
        - René & Angela - I love you more, 1981; SR-23973; René & Angela (Box 412)
          In same jacket as # SR-23974. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SPRO-9644; A-side Matrix # SPRO1-9644-97425 Z1 #1
        - René & Angela - I love you more, 1981; SR-23974; René & Angela (Box 412)
          In same jacket as # SR-23973. 2 copies.
        - Rene Grand Y Su Combo New York - El Gran Rene Grand con Su Combo New York, 1966; SR-23975; Rene Grand Y Su Combo New York; Rodriguez, Frankie (Box 412)
          Catalog # SCLP 9283; A-side Matrix # MC 20507
          Seeco
        - Renegade - Dark soldier part 1 & 2, 1996; SR-23976; Renegade (Box 412)
          Catalog # DREAD 15; A-side Matrix # DREAD 15 A-01-01-1
          Dread Recordings
          Reading, United Kingdom
        - Renegade Foxxx - Nine ways (still hustlin), 2000; SR-23977; Renegade Foxxx; Memphis Bleek (Box 412)
          Catalog # PUSS1001; A-side Matrix # PUSS -1001-B
          PUSS1001
        - Renegade Foxxx - High society for life, 1998; SR-23978; Renegade Foxxx; Red Eye Rum (Box 412)
          Catalog # FOX 3011; A-side Matrix # FOX-3011-A PA 9 99
          TMO / Cool Foxxx Records
        - Renegade Soundwave - Thunder II, 1990; SR-23979; Renegade Soundwave (Box 412)
          Catalog # ED 5502; A-side Matrix # DMS ST-ED-66589-A-1
        - Renegade Soundwave - Ozone breakdown (2004 remixes), 2004; SR-23980; Renegade Soundwave (Box 412)
          Catalog # L 001; A-side Matrix # L 001 A1
        - Renegade Tribe - Hal, 1996; SR-23981; Renegade Tribe (Box 412)
          Catalog # PH-04; A-side Matrix # PH-04 A F/WRCE
          Progressive High
        - Rennie Ren - Brother to brother - stop smoking!, 1985; SR-23982; Rennie Ren (Box 412)
          Catalog # ADP 8985; A-side Matrix # ADP-8985-A
          Connection
        - Rennie Ren - New York woman (of ebony shade), 1984; SR-23983; Rennie Ren (Box 412)
          Catalog # FS 11484; A-side Matrix # B-FS-114 84-A HRM-3
          First String Records
        - Rentie, Morris, Jr. - Do it, jam jam, 1986; SR-23984; Rentie, Morris, Jr. (Box 412)
          Catalog # 2704-1-TPD; A-side Matrix # 2704-1-TPD-AS-1
          Plutonium Records
        - Replacements - I will dare, 1984; SR-23985; Replacements (Box 412)
          Catalog # TTR 8440; A-side Matrix # TTR 8440-A S-12447
          Twin/Tone Records
          Minneapolis, Minnesota
        - Republica - Ready to go, 1996; SR-23986; Republica (Box 412)
          Catalog # RDAB 64539-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB 64539-1-A1
        - REQ - Fantasy roc E.P., 1996; SR-23987; REQ (Box 412)
          Catalog # SKINT 14; A-side Matrix # GRAEME - THE EXCHANGE SKINT 14 A1 O
          Skint
          Brighton, United Kingdom
        - REQ - Fantasy roc E.P., 1996; SR-23988; REQ (Box 412)
          In same jacket as # SR-23989. 2 copies.
        - REQ - Fantasy roc E.P., 1996; SR-23989; REQ (Box 412)
          In same jacket as # SR-23988. 2 copies.
        - Resident Alien - Mr. Boops, 1991; SR-23990; Resident Alien (Box 412)
          Catalog # 44 73974; A-side Matrix # XSS-73974A-1A G1 (T) A4
          Dew Doo Man Records
        - Resistance & D-Tek'D - Losing control; Space jam, 2003; SR-23991; Resistance & D-Tek'D (Box 412)
          Catalog # DZR003; A-side Matrix # DZR003 A 1
          DZ Recordings (DZR)
        - Resonance - After midnight, 1998; SR-23992; Resonance (Box 412)
          Catalog # RESONANCE; A-side Matrix # RESONANCE A1
          Netherlands
        - Retro-Active - Wanna hustle?, 1998; SR-23993; Retro-Active; Garcia, John (Box 412)
          Catalog # GG-1009; A-side Matrix # GG-1009A F/WRCE
          Gossip Records
          Red Bank, New Jersey
        - Return To Forever - Hymn of the seventh galaxy, 1973; SR-23994; Return To Forever; Corea, Chick (Box 412)
          Catalog # PD-5536; A-side Matrix # PD5536-A TR
        - Revanche - Music man, 1979; SR-23995; Revanche (Box 412)
          Catalog # SD 19245; A-side Matrix # ST-A-794313-BBB-1
        - Revanche - You get high in N.Y.C.; Music man, 1979; SR-23996; Revanche (Box 412)
          Catalog # DSKO 185; A-side Matrix # ST-DK-37078-3
        - Revelation - Feel it, 1980; SR-23997; Revelation (Box 412)
          Catalog # AS 887; A-side Matrix # T 1 AS 887AS-1D
          Handshake Records and Tapes
        - Reverberi - Reverberi, 1975; SR-23998; Reverberi (Box 412)
          Catalog # PA 7003; A-side Matrix # PA-7003A GT.
          Pausa Records
          Willowdale, Ontario, Canada
        - Rev. Badoo - Money, money; Talk to them, 1983; SR-23999; Rev. Badoo (Box 412)
          Catalog # JL 025; A-side Matrix # JL 025-A
          Jah Life
        - Paradise Express - Star in my life, 1979; SR-24000; Paradise Express (Box 412)
          Catalog # D-131; A-side Matrix # D-131-A SP KENDUN-A 376
          Fantasy
          Berkeley, California
        - Revival 3000 - The mighty high, 1997; SR-29500; Revival 3000 (Box 412)
          Catalog # 571-809-1; A-side Matrix # Tim D. Masterpiece 571-809-1A1 OR
          Hi Life Recordings